Finding Aid for the Lamar Alexander Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series IV: Governor
  - Sub-series E: Governor’s Papers
    - Education -1984
      - Impact of the Better Schools Program –County Profiles –McMinn-Maury Counties (Box 259, Folder 14)
      - Impact of the Better Schools Program –County Profiles –Meigs-Overton Counties (Box 259, Folder 15)
      - Impact of the Better Schools Program –County Profiles –Perry-Rutherford Counties (Box 259, Folder 16)
      - Impact of the Better Schools Program –County Profiles –Scott-Sumner Counties (Box 259, Folder 17)
      - Impact of the Better Schools Program –County Profiles –Tipton-Wilson Counties (Box 259, Folder 18)
    - Education -1985
      - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 260, Folder 1)
      - Amendments to the Comprehensive Education Reform Act of 1984, 1985 (Box 260, Folder 2)
      - Summary of 1985 Amendments to the Comprehensive Education Reform Act of 1984 (Box 260, Folder 3)
      - Choice (Schools), 1985 (Box 260, Folder 4)
      - State of Education Address by Governor Lamar Alexander, January 1985 (Box 260, Folder 5)
      - Master Plan for Public Education Grades K through 12 –by the Tennessee State Board of Education, January 1985 (Box 260, Folder 6)
      - Address on Education by Governor Lamar Alexander, March 4, 1985 (2) (Box 260, Folder 7)
      - Knoxville News-Sentinel Academic Achievers Banquet –Speech by Lamar Alexander, March 28, 1985 (Box 260, Folder 8)
      - Preliminary Report on Five-Year Comprehensive Education Reform Act of 1984 Goals for K-12, March 1985 (Box 260, Folder 9)
      - Candidate Questionnaire –Career Ladder (Box 260, Folder 10)
      - Career Ladder –Announcements, 1985 (Box 260, Folder 11)
      - Career Ladder After One Year, June 1985 (Box 260, Folder 12)
      - Career Ladder Speech Notes, 1985 (Box 260, Folder 13)
      - Career Ladder Evaluations –Pritchett, King, Smith, 1985 (Box 260, Folder 14)
      - Governor’s Schools (Box 260, Folder 15)
      - Governor’s Schools –Correspondence –Richard Marius, 1985 (Box 260, Folder 16)
      - Tennessee 1985 Reading Assessment –S.R.E.B. Final Report (Box 260, Folder 17)
      - Teacher Orientation Manual, 1985-1985 (2) (Box 260, Folder 18)
      - Tennessee Assessment Center (Box 260, Folder 19)
    - Education -1985-1986
      - Tennessee Model for Pre-First Grade Screening, Summer 1985 (Box 261, Folder 1)
      - Lamar Alexander’s Notes (Box 261, Folder 2)
      - Better Schools Program “It Works”, 1985 (4) (Box 261, Folder 3)
      - Commissioner’s Report Card, 1984-1985 (Box 261, Folder 4)
      - Career Ladder Notes, 1986 (Box 261, Folder 5)
      - Chairs of Excellence, 1985-1986 (Box 261, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 261, Folder 7)
      - Public Education in Tennessee: A Joint Report of the State Board of Education and the T.H.E.C., January 31, 1986 (Box 261, Folder 8)
      - Career Ladder Program –Salary Rankings (Box 261, Folder 9)
      - Carnegie Commission (Box 261, Folder 10)
      - Funding Public Schools –State Board of Education Ad Hoc Committee on Funding, January 23, 1986 (Box 261, Folder 11)
      - State of Education Address, January 1986 (Box 261, Folder 12)
      - State of Education Address –Publication (10) (Box 261, Folder 13)
      - “Student, Teacher and School Performance” A report Submitted to the Governor and the General Assembly by the Board of Education and the Commissioner of Education of the State of Tennessee, February 1, 1986 (Box 261, Folder 14)
    - Education -1986
      - 10 Great Schools –Alcoa Elementary Second Grade, March 1986 (Box 262, Folder 1)
      - 10 Great Schools –Alcoa Elementary Second Grade, March 1986 (Box 262, Folder 2)
      - Kettering Foundation, April 1986 (Box 262, Folder 3)
      - Carnegie Commission, May 1986 (Box 262, Folder 4)
      - Appointment of Dr. Mike Dalton as Assistant Commissioner of the Career Ladder Program, June 1986 (Box 262, Folder 5)
      - “Time for Results: The Governor’s 1991 Report on Education” –Drafts, June 1986 (Box 262, Folder 6)
      - “Time for Results: The Governor’s 1991 Report on Education” –Drafts, July 1986 (1 of 2) (Box 262, Folder 7)
      - “Time for Results: The Governor’s 1991 Report on Education” –Drafts, July 1986 (1 of 2) (Box 262, Folder 8)
      - “Time for Results: The Governor’s 1991 Report on Education” –Drafts (Box 262, Folder 9)
      - “Time for Results: The Governor’s 1991 Report on Education” –Publication, August 1986 (Box 262, Folder 10)
      - Teacher System –Conversion Scales Changes, August 1986 (Box 262, Folder 11)
    - Education -1986-1987
      - Carnegie Forum on Education and the Economy –Report, August 1986 (Box 263, Folder 1)
      - “The Governor’s Job: Getting Ready for 1991” by Lamar Alexander at the National Governors’ Association Meeting, August 6, 1986 (5) (Box 263, Folder 2)
      - Tennessee’s Career Ladder –Brochure, 1986 (Box 263, Folder 3)
      - Better Schools Business Group, Fall 1986 (Box 263, Folder 4)
      - Jack Massey School of Business, 1986 (Box 263, Folder 5)
      - Lamar Alexander’s Notes, 1986 (Box 263, Folder 6)
      - Master plan for Public Education Grades K-12, 1986 by the Tennessee State Board of Education (Box 263, Folder 7)
      - Amendments to the Comprehensive Education Reform Act of 1984, 1986 (Box 263, Folder 8)
      - Weekly Meetings on Career Ladder Program –Agendas, 1986 (Box 263, Folder 9)
      - Career Ladder –Psychiatric Teacher –Counselor Orientation Manual,1986 (Box 263, Folder 10)
      - Highlights of the Governor’s Budget for Higher Education, 1986-1987 (Box 263, Folder 11)
      - Reader’s Digest Article, 1987 (Box 263, Folder 12)
      - Tennessee Comprehensive Education Study, 1981/1982 -1986 Reprint (Box 263, Folder 13)
      - Proposed Agenda for Improving the Quality of Public Post-Secondary Education in Tennessee in the Eighties –Draft (Box 263, Folder 14)
    - Education –School Visits
      - Anderson County (Box 264, Folder 1)
      - Benton County (Box 264, Folder 2)
      - Blount County (Box 264, Folder 3)
      - Blount County –Newspaper Clippings (Box 264, Folder 4)
      - Bradford Special School District (Box 264, Folder 5)
      - Bristol City (Box 264, Folder 6)
      - Carroll County (Box 264, Folder 7)
      - Carter County (Box 264, Folder 8)
      - Chattanooga City (Box 264, Folder 9)
      - Chester County (Box 264, Folder 10)
      - Claiborne County (Box 264, Folder 11)
      - Clay County (Box 264, Folder 12)
      - Cocke County (Box 264, Folder 13)
      - Coffee County (Box 264, Folder 14)
      - Covington Special (Box 264, Folder 15)
      - Crockett County/Bells/Alamo (Box 264, Folder 16)
      - Davidson County (Box 264, Folder 17)
      - Decatur County (Box 264, Folder 18)
      - Dyer County (Box 264, Folder 19)
      - Dyersburg City (Box 264, Folder 20)
      - Fayette County (Box 264, Folder 21)
      - Gibson County (Box 264, Folder 22)
      - Giles County (Box 264, Folder 23)
      - Greene County (Box 264, Folder 24)
      - Greeneville City (Box 264, Folder 25)
      - Hamblen County (Box 264, Folder 26)
      - Hamilton County (Box 264, Folder 27)
      - Harriman City (1 of 2) (Box 264, Folder 28)
      - Harriman City (2 of 2) (Box 264, Folder 29)
    - Education –School Visits
      - Hawkins County (Box 265, Folder 1)
      - Haywood County (Box 265, Folder 2)
      - Henderson County (Box 265, Folder 3)
      - Henry County (Box 265, Folder 4)
      - Hollow Rock/Bruceton (Box 265, Folder 5)
      - Humboldt City (Box 265, Folder 6)
      - Huntington City (Box 265, Folder 7)
      - Johnson City (Box 265, Folder 8)
      - Johnson County (Box 265, Folder 9)
      - Kingsport City (Box 265, Folder 10)
      - Knox County (Box 265, Folder 11)
      - Knoxville City (Box 265, Folder 12)
      - Lebanon City (Box 265, Folder 13)
      - Manchester City (Box 265, Folder 14)
      - McKenzie City (Box 265, Folder 15)
      - McNairy County (Box 265, Folder 16)
      - Memphis City (Box 265, Folder 17)
      - Milan Special School (Box 265, Folder 18)
      - Monroe County (Box 265, Folder 19)
      - Montgomery County (Box 265, Folder 20)
      - Murfreesboro City (Box 265, Folder 21)
      - Oak Ridge City (Box 265, Folder 22)
      - Overton County (Box 265, Folder 23)
      - Paris Special School (Box 265, Folder 24)
      - Roane County (Box 265, Folder 25)
      - Scott County (Box 265, Folder 26)
      - Shelby County (Box 265, Folder 27)
      - South Carroll Special (Box 265, Folder 28)
    - Education –School Visits
      - Sullivan County (Box 266, Folder 1)
      - Sumner County (Box 266, Folder 2)
      - Sweetwater City (Box 266, Folder 3)
      - Tipton County (Box 266, Folder 4)
      - Trenton City Special School (Box 266, Folder 5)
      - Tullahoma City (Box 266, Folder 6)
      - Unicoi County (Box 266, Folder 7)
      - Washington County (Box 266, Folder 8)
      - Wayne County (Box 266, Folder 9)
      - Weakley County (Box 266, Folder 10)
      - West Carroll County (Box 266, Folder 11)
      - White County (Box 266, Folder 12)
      - Whites Creek (Box 266, Folder 13)
      - Wilson County (Box 266, Folder 14)
      - School Visits (Box 266, Folder 15)
      - Report Card Time (Box 266, Folder 16)
      - Letters from School Children (Box 266, Folder 17)
      - Letters from School Children –Alpha Primary, Morristown (Box 266, Folder 18)
      - Letters from School Children –Doak Elementary, Greeneville (Box 266, Folder 19)
      - Letters from School Children –Erwin (Box 266, Folder 20)
      - Letters from School Children –St. Bethlehem School, Clarksville (Box 266, Folder 21)
    - Education –Tennessee Education Association
      - T.E.A. –News Releases, 1977 (Box 267, Folder 1)
      - Presidents List, November 1977 (Box 267, Folder 2)
      - Tennessee Political Action Committee for Education –Pamphlets, 1977 (Box 267, Folder 3)
      - T.E.A. Research Memo, 1975-1978 (Box 267, Folder 4)
      - Tennessee Political Action Committee for Education (T.P.A.C.E.) Handbook, 1978 (Box 267, Folder 5)
      - “T.E.A.’s Priorities –Tennessee’s Future”, 1977-1978 (Box 267, Folder 6)
      - Tennessee Education Association –Legislative Program Pamphlets, 1977/78, 1979/80 (Box 267, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1977-1978, 1981-1985 (Box 267, Folder 8)
      - T.E.A. Response to Budget, 1981 (Box 267, Folder 9)
      - T.E.A. Response to Comprehensive Education Task Force Report, 1982 (Box 267, Folder 10)
      - Legislation –T.E.A. Professional Educator Certification Act, March 30, 1983 (Box 267, Folder 11)
      - “T.E.A. Legislative Report”, March-May 1983 (Box 267, Folder 12)
      - Tennessee School Boards Association -1983 Legislative Program (Box 267, Folder 13)
      - Statement by Marjorie Pike, President of T.E.A. Before Select Committee on Education, August 12, 1983 (Box 267, Folder 14)
      - American Federation of Teachers –News Release, 1983 (Box 267, Folder 15)
      - Special Legislative Session, December 1983 (Box 267, Folder 16)
      - T.E.A. Response Against Master Teacher Program, 1983 (Box 267, Folder 17)
      - T.E.A. News Releases, 1983 (Box 267, Folder 18)
      - Comprehensive Education Reform Act of 1984 –News Releases (Box 267, Folder 19)
      - Governor Lamar Alexander’s State of the State Address to the Tennessee Press Association, January 22, 1984 (Box 267, Folder 20)
      - Message of Governor Lamar Alexander Presented to the 93rd General Assembly of the State of Tennessee (Extraordinary Session), January 10, 1984 (Box 267, Folder 21)
      - T.E.A. Education Excellence Act of 1984 –Draft, January 10, 1984 (Box 267, Folder 22)
    - Education –Tennessee Education Association
      - Tennessee Education, 1983 (Box 268, Folder 1)
      - T.E.A. Educational Excellence Bill, 1984 (Box 268, Folder 2)
      - Tennessee Education, 1984 (Box 268, Folder 3)
      - T.E.A. Bill Notes (Box 268, Folder 4)
      - T.E.A. Career Ladder Impact Study Summary, April 1985 (Box 268, Folder 5)
      - Tennessee Education, 1985 (Box 268, Folder 6)
      - T.E.A. President Will Locke Address to State Board of Education, August 29, 1986 (Box 268, Folder 7)
      - T.E.A. Pamphlets (Box 268, Folder 8)
      - Tennessee Education, 1986 (Box 268, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 268, Folder 10)
      - “Institutional Progress Report on the Holmes Group Agenda” by the University of Tennessee –Knoxville, College of Education, February 1988 (Box 268, Folder 11)
    - Education –Newspaper Clippings, 1976-August 1983
      - 1976-1977 (Box 269, Folder 1)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 269, Folder 2)
      - 1980 (Box 269, Folder 3)
      - 1981 (1 of 2) (Box 269, Folder 4)
      - 1981 (2 of 2) (Box 269, Folder 5)
      - Merit Pay, 1982 (Box 269, Folder 6)
      - January 1983 (Box 269, Folder 7)
      - February 1983 (Box 269, Folder 8)
      - March 1983 (Box 269, Folder 9)
      - April 1983 (Box 269, Folder 10)
      - May 1983 (Box 269, Folder 11)
      - June 1983 (Box 269, Folder 12)
      - July 1983 (Box 269, Folder 13)
      - August 1983 (Box 269, Folder 14)
    - Education –Newspaper Clippings, September 1983-May 1984
      - September 1983 (1 of 2) (Box 270, Folder 1)
      - September 1983 (2 of 2) (Box 270, Folder 2)
      - October 1983 (Box 270, Folder 3)
      - November 1983 (1 of 2) (Box 270, Folder 4)
      - November 1983 (2 of 2) (Box 270, Folder 5)
      - National, 1983 (Box 270, Folder 6)
      - U.S. News & World Report “Merit Pay for Good Teachers?”, 1983 (Box 270, Folder 7)
      - January 1984 (Box 270, Folder 8)
      - February 1984 (Box 270, Folder 9)
      - March 1984 (Box 270, Folder 10)
      - April 1984 (Box 270, Folder 11)
      - May 1984 (Box 270, Folder 12)
    - Education –Newspaper Clippings, June 1984-Undated
      - June 1984 (Box 271, Folder 1)
      - July 1984 (Box 271, Folder 2)
      - August 1984 (Box 271, Folder 3)
      - September 1984 (Box 271, Folder 4)
      - October 1984 (Box 271, Folder 5)
      - November 1984 (Box 271, Folder 6)
      - December 1984 (Box 271, Folder 7)
      - January 1985 (Box 271, Folder 8)
      - March 1985 (Box 271, Folder 9)
      - April 1985 (Box 271, Folder 10)
      - June 1985 (1 of 3) (Box 271, Folder 11)
      - June 1985 (2 of 3) (Box 271, Folder 12)
      - June 1985 (3 of 3) (Box 271, Folder 13)
      - July 1985 (Box 271, Folder 14)
      - August 1985 (Box 271, Folder 15)
      - September 1985 (Box 271, Folder 16)
      - October 1985 (Box 271, Folder 17)
      - November 1985 (Box 271, Folder 18)
      - December 1985 (Box 271, Folder 19)
      - Commercial Appeal –Series on Education, 1985 (Box 271, Folder 20)
      - April 1986 (Box 271, Folder 21)
      - May 1986 (Box 271, Folder 22)
      - November 1986 (Box 271, Folder 23)
      - Undated (Box 271, Folder 24)
    - Environment
      - “An Economic Analysis of a Monitored Retrievable Storage (MRS) Facility for Tennessee,” by the University of Tennessee, November 1985 (Box 272, Folder 1)
      - Articles (Box 272, Folder 2)
      - Baker-Sasser Bill –Great Smoky Mountains National Park Management Plan, 1983 (Box 272, Folder 3)
      - Charles A. Howell’s Address to the Knoxville Rotary Club, January 12, 1982 (Box 272, Folder 4)
      - Clean Water Initiative –Executive Summary (Box 272, Folder 5)
      - Committee for a Clean Tennessee –Newsletter, 1981-1982 (Box 272, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 272, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 272, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 272, Folder 9)
      - Disaster Relief Request, May 1979 (Box 272, Folder 10)
      - Great Smoky Mountain National Park Golden Anniversary Ceremony –Lamar Alexander’s Remarks (Box 272, Folder 11)
      - Information on Beverage Container Litter by William M. Park, 1981 (Box 272, Folder 12)
      - Lamar Alexander Testimony Before Subcommittee on Public Lands and Reserve Water, March 1984 (Box 272, Folder 13)
      - Lists (Box 272, Folder 14)
      - Monitored Retrievable Storage (MRS) –Executive Summary (Box 272, Folder 15)
      - Oak Ridge Community Action (Box 272, Folder 16)
      - Programs, 1985-1986 (Box 272, Folder 17)
      - “Project Roadrunner” by J. Padgett Kelly (Box 272, Folder 18)
      - The Public Response to Monitored Retrievable Storage (MRS) –Report, 1985 (Box 272, Folder 19)
      - Recommendation for Safe Growth Action Team, February 18, 1981 (Box 272, Folder 20)
      - Safe Growth Action Team Member Recommendations (Box 272, Folder 21)
      - Safe Growth Committee Members (Box 272, Folder 22)
      - The Safe Growth Plan (Box 272, Folder 23)
      - Safe Growth Plan –News Releases (Box 272, Folder 24)
      - Safe Growth Team Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 272, Folder 25)
      - Safe Growth Team Goals and Progress, 1984-1985 (Box 272, Folder 26)
      - Safe Growth Team Memos (Box 272, Folder 27)
      - Senate and House Bills (Box 272, Folder 28)
      - Statement of Lamar Alexander Before the Senate Environment and Public Works Committee, March 16, 1981 (Box 272, Folder 29)
      - Tennessee-Tombigee Waterway Development Authority, 1979 (Box 272, Folder 30)
      - Tennessee-Tombigee Waterway –Lamar Alexander’s Notes, 1985 (Box 272, Folder 31)
      - TVA 50th Anniversary Symposium –Lamar Alexander’s Notes (Box 272, Folder 32)
    - General Motors/Saturn Corporation
      - General Motors Chronology with Vonore Area, 1979-1985 (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - Information on Matlock Bend, Loudon County, Tennessee (Box 273, Folder 2)
      - Tellico Lakeside Property (Box 273, Folder 3)
      - Tellico, Tennessee Location, 1985 (Box 273, Folder 4)
      - Key Points for Preliminary Meeting with Governor (Box 273, Folder 5)
      - Lamar Alexander’s Notes (1 of 2) (Box 273, Folder 6)
      - Lamar Alexander’s Notes (2 of 2) (Box 273, Folder 7)
      - Telex from Lamar Alexander to Nissan Chairman Ishihara about Saturn Plant (Box 273, Folder 8)
      - News Release About Upcoming Saturn Decision, July 27, 1985 (Box 273, Folder 9)
      - Facts About Saturn Corporation (Box 273, Folder 10)
      - News Release by Saturn Corporation, July 29, 1985 (Box 273, Folder 11)
      - News Release by Governor About Saturn Plant, July 29, 1985 (Box 273, Folder 12)
      - Saturn Site Announcement –Agenda (Box 273, Folder 13)
      - Maury County Town Meeting Honoring Saturn Corporation, July 30, 1985 (Box 273, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence –Pre-Announcement (Box 273, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence –Post-Announcement (Box 273, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence –Congratulations (1 of 3) (Box 273, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence –Congratulations (2 of 3) (Box 273, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence –Congratulations (3 of 3) (Box 273, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence –Media Attention (1 of 2) (Box 273, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence –Media Attention (2 of 2) (Box 273, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence –Wall Street Journal Advertisement (Box 273, Folder 22)
      - Saturn Advertisement Text –Wall Street Journal (Box 273, Folder 23)
      - Saturn Corporation –Tennessee Site Development Criteria, July 1985 (Box 273, Folder 24)
      - Newspaper Clippings –Pre-Announcement, March 12-July 26 1985 (Box 273, Folder 25)
      - Newspaper Clippings –Post-Announcement, July 27, 1985 (Box 273, Folder 26)
      - Newspaper Clippings –Post-Announcement, July 28-29, 1985 (Box 273, Folder 27)
      - Newspaper Clippings –Post-Announcement, July 30, 1985 (Box 273, Folder 28)
      - Newspaper Clippings –Post-Announcement, July 31, 1985 (Box 273, Folder 29)
    - General Motors/Saturn Corporation to Subaru
      - Newspaper Clippings –Post-Announcement, August 1-4, 1985 (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - Newspaper Clippings –Post-Announcement, August 5-19, 1985 (Box 274, Folder 2)
      - Newspaper Clippings –Post-Announcement, August 20-31, 1985 (Box 274, Folder 3)
      - Newspaper Clippings –Post-Announcement, September 1985 (1 of 2) (Box 274, Folder 4)
      - Newspaper Clippings –Post-Announcement, September 1985 (2 of 2) (Box 274, Folder 5)
      - Newspaper Clippings –Post-Announcement, Undated (Box 274, Folder 6)
      - Articles on Saturn Plant in Tennessee, August 1985 (Box 274, Folder 7)
      - Business Week, August 12, 1985 (Box 274, Folder 8)
      - Capitol Hill: Magazine of the National Republican Club, Summer 1985 (Box 274, Folder 9)
      - Time Magazine, August 5, 1985 (Box 274, Folder 10)
      - Nissan –News Releases, 1980 (Box 274, Folder 11)
      - Nissan, 1980-1983 (Box 274, Folder 12)
      - Nissan –Speech by Lamar Alexander, 1981 (Box 274, Folder 13)
      - Nissan –Newspaper Clippings, 1981 (Box 274, Folder 14)
      - Nissan –Speech by Lamar Alexander at Grand Opening, October 21, 1983 (Box 274, Folder 15)
      - Nissan –Correspondence –Outgoing, 1980 (Box 274, Folder 16)
      - Nissan –Correspondence –Outgoing, 1981 (Box 274, Folder 17)
      - Nissan –Correspondence –Outgoing –Incident at Groundbreaking, 1981 (Box 274, Folder 18)
      - Nissan –Correspondence –Outgoing, 1982 (Box 274, Folder 19)
      - Nissan –Correspondence –Outgoing, 1983 (Box 274, Folder 20)
      - Nissan –Correspondence –Outgoing, 1985 (Box 274, Folder 21)
      - Nissan –Correspondence –incoming, 1980 (Box 274, Folder 22)
      - Nissan –Map of “2000 Population Distribution of the United States” –U.S. Census Bureau (Box 274, Folder 23)
      - Nissan –Newspaper Clippings, October 1985 (Box 274, Folder 24)
      - Subaru –Tennessee Site Information Provided to Fuji Heavy Industries, May 20, 1986 (1 of 5) (Box 274, Folder 25)
      - Subaru –Tennessee Site Information Provided to Fuji Heavy Industries, May 20, 1986 (2 of 5) (Box 274, Folder 26)
      - Subaru –Tennessee Site Information Provided to Fuji Heavy Industries, May 20, 1986 (3 of 5) (Box 274, Folder 27)
    - Subaru to Toyota
      - Subaru –Tennessee Site Information Provided to Fuji Heavy Industries, May 20, 1986 (4 of 5) (Box 275, Folder 1)
      - Subaru –Tennessee Site Information Provided to Fuji Heavy Industries, May 20, 1986 (5 of 5) (Box 275, Folder 2)
      - Toyota –Correspondence –Outgoing, July 17-August 23, 1985 (Box 275, Folder 3)
      - Toyota –Correspondence –Outgoing, August 23-30, 1985 (Box 275, Folder 4)
      - Toyota –Correspondence –Outgoing, November 20-December 24, 1985 (Box 275, Folder 5)
      - Toyota –Correspondence –Incoming, August 28-November 28, 1985 (Box 275, Folder 6)
      - Toyota Motor Corporation –Promotional Materials (Box 275, Folder 7)
      - State of Tennessee Promotional Materials for Toyota (1 of 2) (Box 275, Folder 8)
      - State of Tennessee Promotional Materials for Toyota (2 of 2) (Box 275, Folder 9)
      - State of Tennessee Promotional Materials for Toyota –A Home for Toyota (Box 275, Folder 10)
      - Business Week, November 4, 1985 –Article on Toyota Motor Corporation (Box 275, Folder 11)
    - Legislation, 1979-1981
      - Policy Group Meetings, 1979 (Box 276, Folder 1)
      - Legislative Packets, 1979 (Box 276, Folder 2)
      - News Releases, 1979 (Box 276, Folder 3)
      - Legislative Packets, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 4)
      - News Releases, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 5)
      - Issue Letters to Legislators, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 6)
      - Legislative Packets, 1981 (Box 276, Folder 7)
      - News Releases, 1981 (Box 276, Folder 8)
      - Issue Letters to Legislators, 1981 (Box 276, Folder 9)
      - Messages from the Governor, January-February 1981 (Box 276, Folder 10)
      - Messages from the Governor, March 1981 (Box 276, Folder 11)
      - Messages from the Governor, April 1981 (Box 276, Folder 12)
      - Messages from the Governor, May 1981 (Box 276, Folder 13)
      - Messages from the Governor, June 1981 (Box 276, Folder 14)
      - Messages from the Governor, July 1981 (Box 276, Folder 15)
      - Messages from the Governor, August 1981 (Box 276, Folder 16)
    - Legislation, 1982